I am pretending to be cool.
We are joined by Vanessa Williams.
Which brings us to Devil Wears Prada.
But can you just tell us about the show, how it came about, you know, how fun it is?
Because I'm sure it's a good time.
Well, I am about to leave for London to start rehearsals.
And we open in Plymouth in Devil Wears Prada, which is the southwest part of England.
And Jerry Mitchell, who directed it, he's like a musical theater surgeon.
He'll look at a show and say, this got a book, cut this, add that.
And then he makes it work.
And Elton John is doing the music.
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he said Elton wrote new music.
So he wrote some new music for me.
So it's like a whole new imagination of what it can be and what it should be.
What would the music be for Devil Wears Prada?
My 11th hour number is a total rocker.
It's a banger.
This is when she's on the verge of being ousted.
And the models are going to be walking back and forth.
They're going to freeze.
And I say, you think that I can't see you smugly sitting there with Lee, eager for the ending
you've been waiting years to see.
Today, she's getting ousted, yet her final hour is nigh.
Miranda's reign has run its course.
That's what you think.
Oh, my.
We are.